Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers MS207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1998 -- 2013; MS207.001; 1042 Digital Object(s)
  - Papers, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00746
    - Sudan Update to African Union - Update on Recent Events and Dynamics in Sudan - Draft, 2010-10-10; MS207.001.00792
    - Sudan Update to African Union - Update on Recent Events and Dynamics in Sudan - Draft, 2010-10-11; MS207.001.00793
    - Sudan Update to African Union - Update on Recent Events and Dynamics in Sudan, 2010-10-11; MS207.001.00794
    - Report of the Chairperson of the Commission on the Situation in the Sudan and the Activities of the AUHIP, 2010-11-30; MS207.001.00795
    - AUHIP Activities Report December 2010, 2010-12; MS207.001.00796
    - Monthly Report Juba - November 2011 - Draft, 2010-12-07; MS207.001.00797
    - Brief Update on the Registration Process, 2010-12-10; MS207.001.00798
    - Briefing: Prospects for Peace in Sudan, 2011-01-11; MS207.001.00799
    - Briefing: Prospects for Peace in Sudan, 2011-01-11; MS207.001.00800
    - Briefing on the Technical Constitutional Review Process in Southern Sudan, 2011-03-14; MS207.001.00801
    - Sudan Militias ("Where Militias Vie for Power"), 2011-03-22; MS207.001.00802
    - AUHIP Memo on SSudan Rebellions - MFick, 2011-03-24; MS207.001.00803
    - Briefing South Sudan Rebellions to AUHIP - Draft, 2011-03-27; MS207.001.00804
    - Background and Summary of the Southern Rebellions, 2011-03-28; MS207.001.00805
    - Briefing South Sudan Rebellions to AUHIP - Draft 2, 2011-03-28; MS207.001.00806
    - Security Challenges South Sudan - Briefing of the Security Situation in South Sudan, 2011-03-30; MS207.001.00807; Erasmus, Neha
    - Briefing on the Technical Constitutional Review Process in Southern Sudan, 2011-04-27; MS207.001.00808
    - Summary Note on AUHIP Visit to Southern Sudan, 2011-04-30; MS207.001.00809
    - Summary Note on AUHIP Visit to Southern Sudan, 2011-04-30; MS207.001.00810
    - Summary Note on AUHIP Visit to Southern Sudan, 2011-04-30; MS207.001.00811
    - Briefing to the AUHIP - Summary Briefing and Calendar Rationale, 2011-08-10; MS207.001.00812
    - Briefing to the AUHIP - Summary Briefing and Calendar Rationale, 2011-08-12; MS207.001.00813
    - PSC Report, 2011-10-06; MS207.001.00814; Erasmus, Neha
    - AUHIP Report Plan, 2011-11-10; MS207.001.00815
  - Political Committee, 2011; MS207.001.00816
    - Draft Agenda Political Committee, 2011-03-24; MS207.001.00817
    - Annotated Agenda Political Committee 6-7 April - Draft 1, 2011-04-02; MS207.001.00818
    - Final Draft Citizenship Agreement 2011, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00819
    - Invitation Political Committee 6-7 April, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00820
    - Invitation Political Committee 6-7 April, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00821
    - Proposed Agenda Political Committee Meeting 6-7 Apri, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00822
    - Annotated Agenda Political Committee 6-7 April - Draft 2, 2011-04-04; MS207.001.00823
    - Annotated Agenda Political Committee 6-7 April - Draft 3, 2011-04-04; MS207.001.00824
    - Annotated Agenda Political Committee 6-7 April - Draft 4, 2011-04-05; MS207.001.00825
    - Annotated Agenda Political Committee 6-7 April - Draft 5, 2011-04-05; MS207.001.00826
    - Meeting Notes Political Committee, 2011-04-07; MS207.001.00827
    - Report Political Committee, 2011-04-16; MS207.001.00828
  - Political Frameworks, 2011; MS207.001.00829
    - CDI Suggested inputs on frameworks for interaction, 2011-05; MS207.001.00830
  - Peace Security Council, 2009 -- 2013; MS207.001.00831
    - Communique of the 207th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2009-10-29; MS207.001.00832
      This is about the decisions adopted by The Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU), at its 207th meeting held at the level of Heads of State and Government, in Abuja, Federal Republic of Nigeria, considered the Report of the AU High Level Panel on Darfur (AUPD). The decisions adopted include among others: endorsing the report, reaffirming the commitment of the African Union to combat impunity, and welcoming the progress made by the deployment of UNMID.
      Human rights; Peace; Elections; African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - African Union High-Level Implementation Panel on Sudan Plan of Action, 2010-01-19; MS207.001.00833
      Peace-building; Strategic planning; Violence--Darfur (Sudan); Elections; Conflict Management
    - Report of the Chairperson of the Commission on the Activities of the African Union High-Level Implementation Panel (AUHIP) on Sudan, 2010-07-02; MS207.001.00834
      Darfur (Sudan); Comprehensive Peace Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement, Sudan People's Liberation Army (2005); Boundary disputes; Democratization; Violence--South Sudan; Elections; Political issues; Interregionalism--Sudan; African Union. Peace and Security Council; African Union. High-Level Implementation Pane
    - Final Communique PSC 248th Meeting - Arabic, 2010-11-13; MS207.001.00835
      Document in Arabic
    - Press Release of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union of its 248th Meeting, 2010-11-13; MS207.001.00836
      Peace-building; African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - Press Statement by the African Union on the Protection of Civilians in Armed Conflict, 2011-05-18; MS207.001.00837
      This document is about the 279th meeting held on 18 May 2011 by The Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU) in which it discussed the issue of the protection of civilian populations in armed conflicts, on the basis of the Progress Report of the Chairperson of the Commission on the Development of Guidelines for the Protection of Civilians in African Union Peace Support Operations.
      Somalia; Civilians in war; Armed conflict; African Union
    - Report of the Chairperson of the Commission on the Situation in Sudan, 2011-07-18; MS207.001.00838
      Darfur (Sudan); Political development; Water; Security; Humanitarian Assistance; African Union. Peace and Security Council; UNAMID
    - PSC Report on Sudan - French, 2011-07-18; MS207.001.00839
      Document in French
    - PSC report on Sudan - Arabic, 2011-07-18; MS207.001.00840
    - Communique of the 286th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council, 2011-07-19; MS207.001.00841
      This document is about the situation in Darfur and the activities of the African Union United Nations Hybrid Operation in Darfur (UNAMID)
      Darfur (Sudan); Disarmament; African Union. Peace and Security Council; UNAMID
    - Communique of the 294th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union on the Situation in Libya, 2011-09-21; MS207.001.00842
      African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - PSC Communique - French, 2011-09-21; MS207.001.00843
    - Press Statement of the 295th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2011-09-27; MS207.001.00844
      This document is about the 295th meeting of The Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU), in which it was briefed by the Commissioner for Peace and Security on the activities relating to the AU regional cooperation initiative for the elimination of the Lord's Resistance Army (LRA).
      African Union
    - Communique of the 297th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2011-10-20; MS207.001.00845
      This document is about the decisions adapted in the 297th meeting of The Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU) in regard to the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan and on the activities of the AU High Level Implementation Panel (AUHIP) on Sudan.
      Negotiation--Sudan; African Union
    - Report of the Chairperson of the Commission on the Efforts and Activities of the African Union High-Level Implementation Panel on Sudan, 2011-11-30; MS207.001.00846
      This is a report of the chairperson of the commission on the efforts and activities of the African Union High-Level Implementation Panel on Sudan which consists of two parts: the first provides an overall assessment of the work of the Panel, including the progress made to promote peace, democracy and mutual viability in the Republic of Sudan and the newly independent Republic of South Sudan. The second part consists in an activity report of the AUHIP in the period since its last report to Council, submitted in November 2010.
      Nīl al Azraq (Sudan); Kurdufān al-Janūbīyah (Sudan); Violence--Darfur (Sudan); Democratization; Comprehensive Peace Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement, Sudan People's Liberation Army (2005)--Implementation; South Sudan--Referendum; Transitional justice; Boundary disputes; African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - Communique of the 300th and301th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union on the Situation in Darfur and the activities of the AUHIP, 2011-11-30; MS207.001.00847
      Darfur (Sudan); African Union. Peace and Security Council; African Union. High-Level Implementation Panel; UNAMID
    - Press Statement of the 205th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2011-12-22; MS207.001.00848
      This document is on the implementation of the mandate of the AU Mission in Somalia (AMISOM)
    - PSC 305 Communique on AMISON - French, 2011-12-22; MS207.001.00849
    - Opening Remarks by Ambassador Ramtane Lamamra, Commissioner for Peace and Security - at the 305th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2011-12-22; MS207.001.00850
      This meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union was held on Christmas evening 2011, because of the situation in Somalia.
      Somalia; African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - Communique of the 306th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union on the Situation in Somalia, 2012-01-05; MS207.001.00851
    - PSC 306 Communique on AMISON Strategic Concept - Draft, 2012-01-05; MS207.001.00852
    - Statement by Ambassador Ramtane Lamamra, AU Commissioner for Peace and Security - at the 307th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-01-09; MS207.001.00853
      Africa; African Union. Peace and Security Council; United Nations
    - Communique of the 309th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-01-25; MS207.001.00854
      This document is about the decisions adopted by The Peace and Security Council (PSC) of the African Union (AU), at its 309thmeeting after it was briefed by Ambassador Monica Juma, the Permanent Representative of Kenya to the AU, in her capacity as the Chairperson of the PSC for the month of January 2012, and Ambassador Ramtane Lamamra, the Commissioner for Peace and Security, on the deliberations of the UN Security Council meetings on Somalia and on the AU_UN partnership.
    - Communique of the 310th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-02-14; MS207.001.00855
      This document is about the decision adopted by The Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU) at its 310th meeting held on the status of negotiations between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan on their post_secession relations. The decisions include among others: stressing the concerns about unilateral actions by the two, expressing concerns about border demarcations, and calls on the international community to extend its support to the AUHIP.
      Natural resources; Boundary disputes; African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - Report of the Chairperson of the Commission on the Status of the Negotiation between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan on the Outstanding Issues in their Post-Secession Arrangements, 2012-02-14; MS207.001.00856
      Abyei (Sudan); Petroleum industry and trade; Oil fields; Banks and banking, Central; Currency; Debts, External; Water; Security; Political issues; Boundary disputes; Citizenship; African Union. Peace and Security Council; African Union. High-Level Implementation Panel
    - Press Statement of the 317th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-04-12; MS207.001.00857
      Sudan; South Sudan; Heglig (Kurdufān al-Janūbīyah, Sudan); Armed conflict; Boundary disputes; African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - Communique of the 319th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-04-24; MS207.001.00858
    - Communique of the 319th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-04-24; MS207.001.00859
      This document is about decisions adopted by The Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU) at its 319th meeting at the ministerial level on 24 April 2012 on the situation between Sudan and South Sudan.
      Peace-building; African Union
    - Press Statement of the 319th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-04-24; MS207.001.00860
    - Compliance/Non Compliance of the Republic of South Sudan to the African Union Peace and Security Council decision of 24 April 2012 and the United Nations Security Council Resolution 2046 of 2 May 2012 Endorsing the Roadmap, 2012-06-02; MS207.001.00861
    - Communique of the 327th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-07-14; MS207.001.00862
      Abyei (Sudan); Petroleum industry and trade; Demilitarized zone; Humanitarian Assistance; Civilians in war; Negotiation--Sudan; African Union. Peace and Security Council; African Union. High-Level Implementation Panel
    - Compliance/Non Compliance of the Republic of South Sudan to the African Union Peace and Security Council decision of 24 April 2012 and the United Nations Security Council Resolution 2046 of 2 May 2012 Endorsing the Roadmap, 2012-07-25; MS207.001.00863
    - Communique of the 329th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-08-03; MS207.001.00864
      Nīl al Azraq (Sudan); Kurdufān al-Janūbīyah (Sudan); Boundary disputes; Humanitarian Assistance; Civilians in war; African Union. Peace and Security Council
    - Communique of the 339th Meeting of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union, 2012-10-24; MS207.001.00865
      This document is about decision adopted by The Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU) at its 339th meeting held on 24 October 2012 on the situation between Sudan and South Sudan.
    - Communique of the 353rd Peace and Security Council meeting at the level of Heads of State and Government /Sudan-South Sudan, 2013-01-26; MS207.001.00866
  - Public lectures, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00867
    - Invite SalvaKiir, 2010-01-04; MS207.001.00868
    - Invite Public Lecture, 2010-12; MS207.001.00869
    - Public Lecture Schedule, 2010-12; MS207.001.00870
    - Invitation Thabo Mbeki, 2010-12-23; MS207.001.00871
    - Invite Thabo Mbeki, 2010-12-23; MS207.001.00872
    - Invitation GoSS Cabinet, 2010-12-29; MS207.001.00873
    - Invitation Dr. Riek Machar Teny, 2010-12-29; MS207.001.00874
    - Invitation Dr. Riek Machar Teny, 2010-12-29; MS207.001.00875
    - Invite VP Machar signed, 2010-12-29; MS207.001.00876
    - General Invitation - "Invitation to a Public Lecture by President Thabo Mbeki", 2011-01-01; MS207.001.00877
    - Invite Cabinet signed, 2011-01-02; MS207.001.00878
    - Invite GoSS Cabinet signed, 2011-01-02; MS207.001.00879
    - Speech by Thabo Mbeki, Chairperson of the AUHIP, for the University of Khartoum; Friendship Hall, Khartoum, 2011-01-05; MS207.001.00880
    - Draft Programme - Public Lecture by Pres. Thabo Mbeki, 2011-01-06; MS207.001.00881
    - Address by President Thabo Mbeki AUHIP Juba, 2011-01-07; MS207.001.00882
  - Security, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00883
    - April 2-4 Negotiations, 2011; MS207.001.00884
      - NCP Delegation - List of GOS Participants, 2011-03-28; MS207.001.00885
      - SPLM Delegation - List for members of Lead panel & Security Group travelling to Addis Abba, 2011-03-28; MS207.001.00886
    - Agreed documents, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00887
      - Report of the Security Cluster, 2010-12-07; MS207.001.00888
      - Joint Position Paper on Border Security, 2011-05-30; MS207.001.00889
      - Border Security and JPSM Agreement, 2011-06-29; MS207.001.00890
      - Border Monitoring Agreement, 2011-07-30; MS207.001.00891
      - Kadugli Agreement, 2011-08-08; MS207.001.00892
      - Decision of the First Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-09-18; MS207.001.00893
      - MOU on Non Aggresion and Cooperation Sudan-South Sudan, 2012-02-10; MS207.001.00894
      - Record of Decisions - Meeting of JPSM, 2012-02-10; MS207.001.00895
      - Map of the Centreline of the Temporary Safe Demilitarized Border Zone, 2012-05; MS207.001.00896
    - Unfiled documents, 2011 -- 2012; MS207.001.00897
      - Security Cluster for Post Referendum Issues and Arrangements - Secession Scenario -Consolidated Agreement, 2011-02-02; MS207.001.00898
      - Post Referendum Issues and Arrangements - Security Track - Meeting of Minister of Defence and Minister of SPLA Affairs, 2011-03-19; MS207.001.00899
      - Workshop-Working Notes Security Borders Matrix, 2011-04; MS207.001.00900
      - Joint Position Paper on Border Security - Post-Referendum Negotiations Security Cluster, 2011-04-04; MS207.001.00901
      - NCP/SPLM Joint Recommendation on Agenda (d) - Southerners associated with the Sudan Armed Forces, 2011-04-04; MS207.001.00902
      - Workshop-Working Notes Security Borders Matrix, 2011-04-09; MS207.001.00903
      - SPLA Report Workshop on Security Arrangements in the Two Areas, 2011-04-19; MS207.001.00904
      - SPLA Report Workshop on Security Arrangements in the Two Areas, 2011-04-27; MS207.001.00905
      - CoS Termination of JIU Mandate in Blue Nile and South Kordofan Areas Letter, 2011-05-23; MS207.001.00906
      - Proposed Proposed Concept of Operations Border Security and the Management of the Common Border Zone (CBZ), 2011-05-23; MS207.001.00907
      - Proposal - Interim Security Arrangements for Abyei, 2011-05-28; MS207.001.00908
      - Proposal - Interim Security Arrangements for Abyei, 2011-05-28; MS207.001.00909
      - Security Talks, 2011-05-28; MS207.001.00910
      - Joint Position Paper on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism - SPLM, 2011-05-29; MS207.001.00911
      - Joint Position Paper on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-05-29; MS207.001.00912
      - Post CPA Security Arrangements - SAF Proposal, 2011-05-29; MS207.001.00913
      - Post CPA Security Arrangements - SAF Proposal, 2011-05-29; MS207.001.00914
      - Joint Position Paper on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-05-30; MS207.001.00915
      - Political Framework and Joint Command Mechanism for the Two Areas - Proposal to the Government of Sudan and the SPLM/SPLA (BNS and SKS), 2011-05-30; MS207.001.00916
      - Joint Position Paper on Operationalisation of Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-05-31; MS207.001.00917
      - GoS Letter to UNSC - Position of the Sudanese Government on the issues of post-referendum security arrangements and pending matters, 2011-05-31; MS207.001.00918
      - CoS Meeting Agenda - Security Cluster Meeting: Chiefs of Staff, 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00919
      - CoS Meeting Agenda - Security Cluster Meeting: Chiefs of Staff, 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00920
      - Political Framework and Joint Command Mechanism for the Two Areas - Proposal to the Government of Sudan and the SPLM/SPLA (BNS and SKS), 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00921
      - Summary Security Strategy, 2011-06-02; MS207.001.00922
      - AUHIP Security Plan of Action, 2011-07-19; MS207.001.00923
      - Action points/Decisions AUHIP Internal Meeting on the JPSM, 2012-03-07; MS207.001.00924
      - Concept of Incremental Operationalizing of the JBVMM (Chris changes), 2012-03-07; MS207.001.00925
    - Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00926
      - Report of the 9th Meeting of the Joint Security Cluster Post Referendum Negotiations, 2010-12-07; MS207.001.00927
      - Joint Position Paper on Border Security, 2011-05-30; MS207.001.00928
      - Agreement between the Government of the Sudan and the Government of Southern Sudan on Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-06-29; MS207.001.00929
      - Agreement on the Border Monitoring Support Mission between the Government of Sudan and the Government of South Sudan, 2011-07-30; MS207.001.00930
      - Agreement between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan on Bordering Support Mission - Kadugli Agreement, 2011-08-08; MS207.001.00931
      - First Meeting of the Joint Political and Security Mechanism - Agenda Briefing final powerpoint, 2011-09-18; MS207.001.00932
      - UNISFA Force Commander Brief Border Monitoring Support Mission, 2011-09-18; MS207.001.00933
      - Decision of the First Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-09-18; MS207.001.00934
      - Summary of Decisions of the First Meeting of the JPSM, 2011-09-18; MS207.001.00935
      - Corridors Between the Republic of Sudan (RoS) and the Republic of South Sudan (RoSS) into the Safe Demilitarised Border Zone (SDBZ), 2011-09-19; MS207.001.00936
      - First Meeting of the Joint Political and Security Mechanism between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan - Minutes, 2011-10-18; MS207.001.00937
      - Letter to UN Security Council providing details of additions to the UNISFA mandate for the establishment of a Border Monitoring Support Mission., 2011-10-18; MS207.001.00938
      - Note of the Joint Secretariat of the JPSM, 2011-10-20; MS207.001.00939
      - Brief on the JPSM: Area of Operations of the SDBZ, 2011-10-23; MS207.001.00940
      - Thabo Mbeki Note Verbale AUHIP, 2011-11-09; MS207.001.00941
      - Thabo Mbeki Note Verbale AUHIP, 2011-11-09; MS207.001.00942
      - Thabo Mbeki Note Verbale AUHIP, 2011-11-09; MS207.001.00943
      - Thabo Mbeki Note Verbale AUHIP, 2011-11-09; MS207.001.00944
      - Thabo Mbeki Note Verbale AUHIP, 2011-11-09; MS207.001.00945
      - Draft Note on the JPSM, 2011-12-09; MS207.001.00946
      - Note on the Area of Operations of the SDBZ, 2011-10-19; MS207.001.00947
      - Proposed Joint Political and Security Mechanism (JPSM) Meeting January 2012, 2012-01-06; MS207.001.00948; Erasmus, Neha
      - Proposed Joint Political and Security Mechanism (JPSM) Meeting January 2012, 2012-01-09; MS207.001.00949
      - Draft Letter Thabo Mbeki to H.E. Min John Kuong - JPSM, 2012-01-10; MS207.001.00950
      - Proposed Joint Political and Security Mechanism (JPSM) Meeting January 2012 - for Parties, 2012-01-15; MS207.001.00951
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Gen. John Kong Nyuong/GoRSS, 2012-01-15; MS207.001.00952
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Gen. John Kong Nyuong/GoRSS, 2012-01-15; MS207.001.00953
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Lt-Gen Abdel Raheem Mohamed Hussein/GoS, 2012-01-15; MS207.001.00954
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Lt-Gen Abdel Raheem Mohamed Hussein/GoS, 2012-01-15; MS207.001.00955
      - Proposed Joint Political and Security Mechanism (JPSM) Meeting January 2012 - Secretariat, 2012-01-19; MS207.001.00956
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to General Tesfay Tadesse/UNISFA, 2012-01-19; MS207.001.00957
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to General Tesfay Tadesse/UNISFA, 2012-01-19; MS207.001.00958
      - Letters, 2012-02; MS207.001.00959
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Gen. John Kong Nyuong, 2012-02-03; MS207.001.00960
      - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to General Tesfay Tadesse/UNISFA, 2012-02-05; MS207.001.00961